Who likes good news?
Everyone? Then, good news, everyone.
Our next delivery isn't to
some dangerous outer space planet.
It's to Earth.
Earth is dangerous.
I fell off my chair there once.
Ow!
Quit it, Earth.
We won't even have to leave
New New York.
The package is going to Long Long Island.
Yes, to the lavish Mafia-style villa
of the Donbot.
The Donbot? The vicious Robot Gangster?
I'd better use my special robot vision
to see what's inside.
It looks like a pair of clamps.
When are those new clamps
going to get here?
These are all rusted out
with snitch juice.
Patience, Clamps,
it is my eldest daughter's wedding day.
You don't want the Space Pope
to see you clamping, now, do you?
Oh, geez, I forgot my Pope manners.
Dearly beloved,
it is with the great speed that I now
pronounce you husband and wife.
-Hey!
-What the...
May I help you with some assistance?
Delivery for Francis X. Clampazzo?
We don't got nobody here by that alias.
Hey, hey, that's me.
Are those my new clamps?
Your name's Francis?
Oh!
Guys, look, it's Calculon,
and the Robot Devil, and an open bar.
What's not to sneak into?
Bender, you can't crash a mob wedding.
You forget, Leela.
I'm Bender, owner of disguise.
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
my good friend, Calculon.
Hey, this one's for the new couple.
It's your day. It's all about you.
Who's that singing at your wedding?
It's Calculon, Calculon, Calculon
Hey. Oh. Piscopo. This guy.
Bada-boing.
Hey, sexy, I'm Bender.
What brings you to this tacky soirée?
-I'm the bride.
-Oops.
How about you, baby? Want to do it?
-Bender, it's me, Fanny.
-You who?
The Donbot's wife?
We had an affair.
An affair, huh? Sounds like me.
Geez, I'd better be a little more careful.
I don't want to hit on anybody
I already had sex with.
Hiya, Bella.
Hi, Mom.
What about you? You're my third choice.
Oh, Bender,
this is all happening too slowly.
Let's get married.
Quiet, I'm making out with a floozy.
Hold your clapper. Someone's coming.
Donbot, please, I'll pay you back
as soon as you lend me some more money.
Sorry, Calculon.
It gives me no joy to do this,
because Clamps will be doing it.
Clamps, here are your new clamps.
Clamps!
No, no.
Line?
No!
Yeah, Daddy hates welchers.
The only thing he hates worse
is witnesses.
And guys who mess around
with his daughters.
And attempt to duplicate
his meatball recipe.
How was the wedding, Bender?
Says who? I didn't witness anything!
In entertainment news,
two-time Oscar pool winner, Calculon,
was brutally clamped yesterday
by an unknown assailant.
Poor Calculon.
All right, Amy, you win!
The mob did it.
I saw the whole thing while also having
hot sex with the Donbot's daughter.
I'm scared and great at sex.
Bender, you need to go to the police
and tell them a tastefully edited version
of what you just said.
What, and have the Mafia
come after me, too?
No way. This secret goes to my grave.
The Bureau is offering anyone
with information
about this gangland-style clamping
a $50 reward.
Ooh! Ooh!
And then Calculon said, "No, no. No!"
And then I ate some excellent meatballs.
Can I have my 50 bucks now?
I enjoyed your story,
especially the tasteful love scene,
but it's not enough to convict the Donbot.
You'll have to testify in open court.
No. No!
Can I have another $50?
-No.
-No?
-No!
All rise for the Honorable Judge 723.
Be seated.
Organized crime
is a plague on our society,
and I will not tolerate
any form of intimidation during...
All rise for the Honorable Judge 724.
Good day. I'd like to say
I'm prepared to tolerate several,
if not all forms of intimidation
during this trial.
Prosecutor?
Your Honor, the prosecution pecks
for a mistrial
on the grounds of jury tampering.
-Donbot?
-Motion denied.
Prosecutor, call your first witness.
The People call our star witness, Mr. X,
whose appearance will be altered
because he's in grave danger.
Bender, I've been looking for you.
Which cake do you like better
for our wedding?
Bender?
Fix it, fix it, fix it, fix it!
Whew, that was close.
Isn't it true, Mr. X, that you are
slandering this innocent Mafioso
to distract from your own felonious past,
including a crime you made up yourself
called "burgle-arson-arceny"?
That's a wholly-owned trademark
of Rodriguez Crime Concepts, Inc.
Besides, I'm not on trial here.
That's true.
You're on trial in Courtroom Three.
You are charged with two counts
of burgle-arson-arceny.
How do you plead?
Not inno-guilty-cent.
And then the Donbot said,
"Sorry, Calculon,"
and then Calculon said, "No!"
I think we've heard enough.
Wait, I'm not finished. "O!"
Now I'm finished.
Your Honor, the prosecution roosts.
Have you reached a verdict?
Indeed.
After a steamy 12-way deliberation,
we find the accused guilty as...
Wait.
The Donbot is innocent.
Calculon, who is that escorting you?
Yes, who?
My personal trainer,
and he's trained me to say
that my wounds were self-inflicted,
for, you see, I am a big, Hollywood idiot,
dumb guy what does that sort of thing.
Perfect.
We find the Donbot...
Dramatic pause.
Not guilty.
What?
Honey, if you're marrying Bender,
you might want to get a black dress
for the wedding.
That's going to look hot.
Don't be scared, Bender.
We're putting you
in the Witness Relocation Program.
You'll be given a new identity,
a new place to live, and this iPod.
I don't want it anymore.
So I gotta hide forever?
No, just until the Robot Mafia
finds and kills you.
They're pretty good at that.
Goodbye, Professor.
Before I leave, I just want you to know
I've never done any work whatsoever.
Zoidberg, I know it seems
like I can't stand you.
Leela, you'll have to watch out
for Fry now.
Oh, Lord.
I wish I could go with you, pal.
Me, too. I'll need a butler.
Bender, we have to go.
There'll never be another like him.
Let's hire someone better.
Clamps. Clamps!
Huh?
Listen to my boss words.
I would like you
to apply for Bender's old job
and cozy up to this Fry, his best friend.
Yeah, and then I'll introduce him
to my best friend,
clamp number one!
Sorry, toots.
No, Clamps. No clamps.
Sooner or later, Bender will contact Fry
as relocated-squealers always do.
Then with the clamps, Francis.
Francis... Francis?
I'll clamp you with the Francis!
Hey, whoa! Take it ease.
Hey there, slick, I'm here about the job.
Take a seat.
We'll begin the interview shortly.
We'll start with Andrew.
Yeah, they all kind of broke.
So, when do I start?
Everyone, this is Francis.
-Hey, Francis.
-Hello, Francis.
-Hello.
-Cute name.
Look what he can do.
-Wow!
-Whoa!
Yeah, I do it all.
Clamping, crimping, occasional snipping.
Snipping?
Looks like you
may be out of a job, Zoidberg.
That's all good fun,
but of course a clamp is no substitute
for the precision of a genuine...
Francis, would you do the honors?
Stay off my turf!
Yeesh. That guy can bite
my shiny metal clamps.
You remind me
of my old friend Bender.
Oh, yeah? Where does he safely live?
I don't know.
Hey, you want to come to my house
and play?
Yeah, sounds like freakin' fun.
Four stinking years of clamping school
for this?
Greetings, Francis.
Sorry if I was a little hostile before,
but snipping is the only reason
I'm even tolerated around here.
Not like you,
with those magnificent squeezers.
Squeezers? Squeezers?
They're clamps, you!
And if I want to -ing
snip with these clamps,
I will snip with these -ing clamps!
Why do you think they call me...
Francis?
Francis, I have good news!
It's time for your first delivery.
To the Moon!
Fan--ing-tastic!
Here's the 200 feet of rope you ordered,
Sheriff Furley.
Hot diggity! You fellers want to
stick around for the hanging tomorrow?
It's gonna be a doozy.
I sure do love hanging people.
Well, I best start cutting the nooses.
Oh! You know who could help with that?
Francis!
Nice job, Francis.
I like how you didn't get drunk and
steal anyone's organs, like our old robot.
Bender?
Bender, it's me, Fry!
Hyah!
I knew Bender would turn up
purely by coincidence.
Take care of him, but do it quietly.
Don't worry. We're in space,
where no one can hear you clamp.
What do you know?
The Feds gave Bender a new identity
as a Moon farmer.
He must be afraid to break character,
in case there's any Robot Mafia
scuzzballs around.
- Heh?
- Come on, let's go check on him.
I checked on a guy once.
I checked him into tiny pieces!
Bender? Nope, don't recollect nobody
by that name.
But let me ask my son-in-law. Billy?
Yes, Moon-Pa?
These nice big-city hillbillies are
looking for someone named Bender.
You know him?
Nope. He ain't any
of the eight people I ever met.
Bender, it's us, your friends.
You can drop the hillbilly moron act.
Sorry, mister, but I'm no Bender.
I'm just a simple farmer.
Name's Billy West.
Billy West?
What a stupid, phony, made-up name.
You city folk are probably hungry
from premarital sex and flag-burning.
Y'all wanna stay for supper?
Well, my boyfriend and I were going
to have sex on a burning flag,
but I could have a bite.
May I present my beautiful robot wife,
the Crushinator.
She's serving up the dinner and the charm.
-Mashed chicken, Mr. Fry?
-Sure.
So, uh, Billy, where were you born?
Right here in Moon country.
And how long have you been a farmer?
Reckon I was born a farmer.
Folks say my mama was a hoe.
Oh, dear, I seem to have warped my fork.
Could you bend it back for me, Billy?
Bend it? I can't even lift it.
Which is weird, seeing as how
my daddy was a forklift.
Wow. Bender is really committed
to his new Jethrovian identity.
If y'all are finished, I'll drive
y'all back to town in the old clunker.
So, y'all flew here in a spacey ship?
Stop talking like that!
You live on the Moon!
If that is Bender, I guess he's just
happier in his new life.
I refuse to believe anyone is happy!
Mr. West, would you mind
if I examined your brain?
Examine?
Heck, if you can find it, you can keep it.
Gadzooks! Bender's hard drive no longer
contains any of his old memories!
When the Feds bumpkinized him,
they completely wiped out
his old identity!
Well, I don't know about that,
but who am I to argue
with a man from the sky?
So long, space heroes.
You sure you don't want
to kill all humans?
I love all humans.
He really is gone.
I guess I'm happy for him.
And honestly, Francis is a way
better friend than Bender ever was.
Hey, where is Francis?
One sarsapar-oil-la, Sheriff. I'm thirsty.
Make it two. I'm greedy.
You got the rest fooled, but not me.
Now let's take this outside,
so's no one else gets clamped.
You're the boss, stranger.
I'm gonna clamp your body parts off
one by one.
But then I'm gonna clamp your wounds
shut so you stay alive
while I clamp you some more!
Say your prayers, stoolie.
Okay. God bless Grandma and Grandpa...
They're next! Right now,
I'm gonna cut your damn head off!
Drop the robot!
I thought I told you,
I do the cutting around here.
Scuttle on home.
This ain't none of your business, slick.
My name isn't Slick. It's Zoidberg.
John -ing Zoidberg!
Stop! Zoidberg, you'll hurt Francis!
Oh, yeah? Take this and that!
Why, you lousy...
I'm gonna clamp your...
Oh, yeah.
Ow, ow, ow.
Looks like an all-you-can-kill
lobster fest!
That offer was for a limited time only.
My clamps!
Why, Zoidberg, why?
Because our friend Francis here,
is in reality a bad murderer.
Yup. He was fixin' to kill me.
This here crawdad done saved my life!
Bender, you two-timing jerk!
I put off my singing career for you!
If I can't have you, no one can!
Oh, shucks.
Bender! No!
What?
Bender was a hell of a squealer.
Maybe the best there ever was.
We'll send his widow some meatballs.
Clamps, Bella, get in the way-back.
To my friend, Bender.
A wise man once said
he was a hell of a squealer.
Maybe the best there ever was.
To Bender!
You pizza's gonna be another minute.
We still waiting for it to be delivered.
Bender?
I'm no Bender.
You got me mixed up with another robot.
You're probably right.
I don't really remember
what he looks like.
Guys, guys, it's me, Bender.
He's alive!
So that Moon hillbilly who got murdered
was just an innocent husband and father.
Bender, old 'bot,
the Mafia thinks you're dead.
You can come back to work with us.
I'm back, baby!
Pizza's here.
Whoo!
I'll just cut that...
You do, and I'll -ing
gut you like a fish.